Office of Community Relations Records UA233
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Campus files, 1973 -- 2016; UA233.003; 3.58 Linear Feet 3 record cartons and 1 12" LP box
  - Honkfest, 2007 -- 2009; UA233.003.012.00087; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Mulberry Child Care, 1998; UA233.003.012.00088; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Powderhouse School, 2009 -- 2012; UA233.003.012.00089; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Property issues, 1980 -- 1982, 2009 -- 2010; UA233.003.012.00090; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Raise the Roof Concert (respond), 1987 -- 1989, 2005; UA233.003.012.00091; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Rats - West Somerville (2012), 2011 -- 2012; UA233.003.012.00092; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - School Work (Somerville and Medford), 1999; UA233.003.012.00093; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Shape Up Somerville, 2004; UA233.003.012.00094; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Somerville Arts Council, 2001 -- 2004, 2016; UA233.003.012.00095; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Somerville Board of Aldermen, 1979 -- 2005; UA233.003.012.00096; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Somerville City Government, 1973 -- 1984; UA233.003.012.00097; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - SCATV (Somerville Community Access Television), 2005 -- 2015; UA233.003.012.00098; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Somerville Community Housing, 1989, 2002; UA233.003.012.00099; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Health information, 2001 -- 2006; UA233.003.012.00100; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Somerville Community Support, 2011; UA233.003.012.00101; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Somerville Conversations Project, 1996 -- 1998; UA233.003.012.00102; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Somerville/Home First Charitable Corporation, 1991 -- 1993; UA233.003.012.00103; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Somerville Homeless Coalition, 2004 -- 2008, 2013 -- 2016; UA233.003.012.00104; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Somerville - Housing Affordable Housing Trust Fund, 1989, 1992; UA233.003.012.00105; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Somerville land court, 1992; UA233.003.012.00106; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Somerville lodging licenses, 2003 -- 2004, 2009 -- 2010; UA233.003.012.00107; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Somerville mayors, 1980 -- 2013; UA233.003.012.00108; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Somerville misc., 2005 -- 2015; UA233.003.012.00109; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Somerville mural copy of drawing, circa 2000 -- 2015; UA233.003.012.00110; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Somerville politics, 1999 -- 2015; UA233.003.012.00111; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Somerville projects zoning, 1986 -- 1995, 2006; UA233.003.012.00112; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Somerville Public Schools, 2008; UA233.003.012.00113; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Somerville Public Schools, 2007; UA233.003.012.00114; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Somerville Public Schools misc., 1995 -- 2000; UA233.003.012.00115; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Somerville Public Schools misc., 2001 -- 2013; UA233.003.012.00116; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Somerville Public Schools Youth Career Connect, 2014; UA233.003.012.00117; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Somerville Support FY14 (cont.), 2013 -- 2014; UA233.003.013.00118; 1 Folder(s) (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Somerville Support FY15 (cont.), 2014 -- 2015; UA233.003.013.00119; 1 Folder(s) (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Somerville Support FY14, 2013 -- 2014; UA233.003.013.00120; 1 Folder(s) (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Somerville Support FY16, 2015 -- 2016; UA233.003.013.00121; 1 Folder(s) (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Somerville Support FY16 (cont.), 2015 -- 2016; UA233.003.013.00122; 1 Folder(s) (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Somerville Support FY15, 2014 -- 2015; UA233.003.013.00123; 1 Folder(s) (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Somerville Task Force, 1986 -- 1988; UA233.003.013.00124; 1 Folder(s) (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Somerville vocational education, 2010 -- 2015; UA233.003.013.00125; 1 Folder(s) (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - SPELL Somerville Schools, 2002, 2010; UA233.003.013.00126; 1 Folder(s) (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Students' Rights and Employment, 1985 -- 1990; UA233.003.013.00127; 1 Folder(s) (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Walnut Street Center, Inc., 2003 -- 2004; UA233.003.013.00128; 1 Folder(s) (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - West Somerville Neighborhood Association, 2012; UA233.003.013.00129; 1 Folder(s) (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - West Somerville Neighborhood School, 1996 -- 1997; UA233.003.013.00130; 1 Folder(s) (Box 13, Folder 13)